Gosh, that's nice.
DAY BEFORE HIKE
YEONGNAM ALPS BASE CAMP
TARZZAN IS ON THE PHONE WITH SOMEONE
Hey, guys.
Bailey wants to say hi to you.
Cha.
Jung-won.
SORRY FOR BEING SILLY
NEXT, HE INTRODUCES DOWOON
I'm telling her you're a drummer!
I'm a drummer.
Hello.
And the one who's an actor
is in the bathroom.
THE SWEET BAILEY WISHES THEM
A SAFE HIKE TOMORROW
Let's plan the schedule quickly
before we shower.
Okay.
The Yeongnam Alps.
THE MEMBERS HAVE GATHERED
TO PLAN THE THIRD HIKE
Which mountains are we climbing again?
The mountains we'll attempt
to climb tomorrow are…
THE THIRD QUEST
Three peaks of the Yeongnam Alps.
OUT OF THE 9 PEAKS OF THE YEONGNAM ALPS
THE 1-DAY
3-PEAK
CHALLENGE
DIFFICULTY: MODERATE
WALK THE RIDGE
WALK IT
AND KEEP WALKING IT
BAENAEGOGAE PARKING LOT, GANWOLSAN,
SINBULSAN, YEONGCHUKSAN
TOTAL HIKING DISTANCE OF ABOUT 16 KM
First off,
how long does it take to get there?
About ten minutes.
-From here?
-Yes.
We'll be going to a place called
Baenaegogae Parking Lot.
TAKES LESS THAN 10 MINUTES BY CAR
FROM BASE CAMP TO STARTING POINT
SCHEDULED TO START HIKING AT 8:00 A.M.
If we start at 8:00 a.m. to hike…
Then, should we put
wake-up time at 7:00 a.m.?
-At 7:00 a.m. and…
-Get up at 7:10 a.m.?
-You can wake up anytime.
-It's up to us?
But at 7:20 a.m.,
Lee Chae-min and Lee Chae-won will eat.
At 7:20 a.m., Chae and Chae will eat.
-Chae and Chae will eat.
-Okay.
Then, we'll leave at 7:45 a.m.
7:45 A.M.
LEAVE BASE CAMP
IN COMMAND
Sounds good.
This is important.
It'll get us up at 7:00 a.m.
-Exactly.
-"Depart."
You can brush teeth
and wash your face in five minutes.
At 8:00 a.m., we start climbing.
-"Climbing starts."
-That's right.
This is a pure Korean word.
You have nice handwriting.
CHUCKLING
8:00 A.M.
START CLIMBING
You said the first mountain
takes an hour to climb, right?
It takes about two hours to the peak.
GANWOLSAN
Two hours?
Then, we should arrive by 10:00 a.m.
If you walk down from Ganwolsan
for about 30 minutes,
there's a silver grass field
called Ganwoljae.
It has a rest area and a cafeteria there.
They sell cup noodles.
You can eat them there with hot water.
GANWOLJAE, WHERE THE WIND RESTS
They sell roasted eggs
and instant rice too.
Let's eat at 10:30 a.m.
LUNCH SCHEDULED FOR 10:30 A.M.
We'll eat ramyeon and eggs there.
We'll set off again at 11:00 a.m.
We'll check our gear before we leave.
And we should arrive at 12:00 p.m.
At 12:00 p.m.
Hey, at the top of Sinbulsan,
let's shout "Yahoo!"
We haven't done that yet.
They said we can't shout.
We can't do that nowadays?
HIKING ETIQUETTE
REFRAIN FROM SHOUTING
TO NOT STARTLE WILD ANIMALS OR HIKERS
A silent "Yahoo."
A silent "Yahoo" sounds good.
DEPART FROM SINBULSAN
AFTER SILENT YAHOO AT 12:05 P.M.
So if we walk the ridge
to the next peak, that'll take…
About one and a half hours.
The time it takes to see it?
We're fast, so let's be there by 1:30 p.m.
We'll cut it by five minutes.
It's the last peak and mountain,
so tell the viewers
how you felt being on the show.
Let's finish all of that in one minute.
Of course, we know
the production crew works very hard.
But last time, at Baengnokdam,
they wasted a lot of time.
Well, it was exactly nine minutes.
-Really?
-Yes.
It must've felt long because we waited.
It was nine minutes minus the wait?
When these two arrived,
we just took a quick photo
and went straight down.
Is that so? Thank you for your hard work.
EMBARRASSED GARDEN
I look forward to your cooperation
this time around too.
And tomorrow…
The most important thing is
we'll be hiking together tomorrow.
That means Hyun-yong
is going to explain stuff to us again.
You all are too kindhearted,
but at least for that moment,
put that kindness of yours away.
DECLARES NO SIGHTSEEING
Why are we going to the mountains then?
PRESIDENT TAR'S SHARP WORDS
Aren't we going for that?
That's why it's driving me mad.
THE ONE SUPPOSEDLY GOING MAD
CAUGHT RED-HANDED
TAKING PHOTOS OF THE MOUNTAIN
What's gotten into you?
It's just for the sake of it.
It is pretty beautiful here.
SHY GARDEN
This place definitely has
the prettiest view.
The reed field is pretty here.
I see why they'd shoot TV shows here.
Honestly, I kind of like these.
This is actually the first time
I've thought a mountain looked nice.
This mountain is the best one.
Ulsan is nice.
CAR, THE GARDEN WILL BE DRIVEN MAD
BY YEONGNAM ALPS' BEAUTY
Was it three hours to descend?
-Two and a half.
-Two and a half?
Let's aim to finish the descent
by 4:00 p.m.
We'll pick up the pace.
We always finish descending
around 4:00 p.m.
DESCEND CLUB HAS DEVELOPED A ROUTINE
Let's go with this.
APPROVED BY THE MANAGER
The president should sign it too.
You need to sign after me to finalize it.
In this small spot.
TINY
I think you signed in my spot.
That's a cool signature.
It looks like graffiti.
APPROVED BY PRESIDENT TAR
Mine's simple.
MINISTER OF FOREIGN AFFAIRS APPROVES
It can't be simpler than mine.
Hey, what is that?
-Dowoon.
-It's "Do."
Isn't this just a checkmark?
SUPER SIMPLE
This is actually a "DW."
THE MINISTER OF TRANSPORT APPROVES
The schedule looks good today.
A THOROUGH PLAN BEFITTING
OF THE 3-PEAK CHALLENGE
THE YEONGNAM ALPS
CLIMBING SCHEDULE IS COMPLETE
Good night, guys.
Good night. Good work today.
EVERYONE GOES TO BED
CHAE AND CHAE HAVE BREAKFAST
EATING EGGS AND BANANAS
DOWOON IS STILL ASLEEP
GROANING
GRUNTS
I had a dream
where we climbed Mount Everest.
Gosh, how horrible.
CAN'T STOP THINKING ABOUT
HIS HIKING NIGHTMARE
EVEN THOUGH HE'S STILL HALF-ASLEEP
MAKES SURE TO LAYER
HIS CLOTHES THOROUGHLY
CAR, THE GARDEN IS READY
You have the legs of a model.
You have the upper body of a UFC fighter,
but your lower body is that of a model.
Someone said this to me last time.
It was the first time we ever met.
They looked at my legs
and said, "You have Nine Muses' legs."
"Your upper body is pretty big."
THE WORST PHYSIQUE FOR HIKING
"But you have Nine Muses' legs."
Hello. The weather is nice.
Why are your pants down so low?
Sorry?
The waist is too big.
-Is that the reason?
-Yes.
-Is it unintentional sagging?
I don't sag my pants when I hike.
It's too cold.
While doing this show, I started spending
less effort on being stylish.
That's how hard it is.
Hiking, that is.
It makes someone who loves to look cool
pull up his pants.
That's what hiking does.
Gosh.
EXCLAIMING
THE REAL MODEL IS HERE
You're K2 personified.
Come on, you're the same.
I'm in the minor leagues with K2.
"Minor leagues."
Watch K2 send me an official letter.
"We ask that you not wear
our brand's products
on a show ever again."
I heard you had a good dream, Dowoon.
-Sorry?
-I heard you had a good dream.
I woke up screaming.
Since it was in your dream,
I should send you there.
What are you talking about?
For the first time,
I got to sleep for seven hours
before going hiking.
It's so nice to get some good sleep
before we hike.
I'm feeling great.
Yes, I feel really good.
THEY SET OFF IN GOOD CONDITION
Today, we just need to tough it out
during school hours.
That's right.
Goodness.
It sure is cool.
I don't see any high mountains.
Maybe we're climbing three of those.
I think so.
-That must be the route.
-Yes.
Along the ridge.
Still, let's warm up our ankles and knees
so we won't get injured.
Let's do it.
143 BAENAEMUDEUNGGOL-GIL, SANGBUK-MYEON,
ULJU-GUN, ULSAN, KOREA
BAENAEGOGAE PARKING LOT
I bet we won't need crampons at all today.
No, I don't think we'll need them.
I think we'll only have to wear
a thin pair of gloves too.
Yeah, a thin pair.
Exactly.
TODAY'S HIKE IS DIFFERENT FROM THE OTHERS
A NON-FROZEN TRAIL
THAT DOESN'T NEED CRAMPONS
THE SUN WAS ALREADY UP 1 HOUR AGO
WARM ENOUGH OF A TEMPERATURE AT 2.1°C
FOR MOUNTAIN BIRDS TO WAKE UP
GENTLE WIND BLOWING SOUTHWEST
AT 0.9 M/S
BUT IN REALITY, IT'S A STRONG WIND
The wind's stronger than expected.
NARROW TERRAIN AND HIGH ALTITUDE
MAKE THE WIND BLOW HARDER
Things aren't right.
What is this?
We have to go up quickly.
BEFORE GOING UP
PEAK 1
GANWOLSAN
PEAK 2
SINBULSAN
PEAK 3
YEONGCHUKSAN
YEONGNAM ALPS' 3-PEAK CHALLENGE
TODAY'S HIKING TRAIL
IF YOU CLIMB THE ENDLESS STAIRS
AND PASS THROUGH THE SCREE TRAIL
PEAK 1 CONQUERED
GANWOLSAN
DESCEND ALONG
GOLDEN SILVER GRASS FIELDS
GANWOLJAE, THE SILVER GRASS FIELD
BETWEEN GANWOLSAN AND SINBULSAN'S RIDGES
TOWARD PEAK 2
ASCENDING AGAIN
KEEP GOING UP AND DOWN ALONG THE RIDGE
PEAK 2 CONQUERED
SINBULSAN
HIKE ALONG THE RIDGE
BETWEEN THE SILVER GRASS FIELDS AGAIN
CLIMB OVER THE FOLLOWING PATH
WITH BIG ROCKS
PEAK 3 CONQUERED
YEONGCHUKSAN
BAENAEGOGAE PARKING LOT, GANWOLSAN,
SINBULSAN, YEONGCHUKSAN
HIKING DISTANCE: ABOUT 10 KM
ESTIMATED TIME: 5 HOURS AND 30 MINUTES
HIKING STARTS
It's going to be a bit chilly.
Yeah.
It's an aggressive wind.
It's cold.
A BIT CHILLY DUE TO THE STRONG WIND
We're not wearing crampons.
THEIR FIRST HIKE WITHOUT CRAMPONS
It's nice.
THE SEONGPANAK TEAM
TAKES LEAD SIDE BY SIDE
Hey, slow down!
Sorry?
Someone said something.
Someone said something?
Go slow.
IT'S PRODUCER NAH
PRODUCER NAH'S PLEA WAS BURIED BY THE WIND
Someone said, "Go slow."
It's just some old guy from town.
LONELY
What's with this incline?
TODAY'S HIKING TRAIL
IS STEEP FROM THE START
It's crazy from the get-go.
SIGHING
It feels strange without crampons.
THEY WALK PAST THE STEEP INCLINE
IN AN ENVIRONMENT DIFFERENT FROM BEFORE
It's all stairs from this point,
and it'll be tough.
FROM HERE TO THE HIGHEST PEAK
THEY'LL CLIMB ABOUT 1 KM OF STAIRS
LEAD: CAR, THE GARDEN AND CHAE-MIN
MIDDLE: DOWOON
TAIL: TARZZAN
WALKING STRONG IN A 2-1-1 FORMATION
This really is like a StairMaster here.
TAKING OFF HIS HAT
The path had stairs from the start.
It was warm too.
And certain parts of your muscles
are used for climbing stairs,
like on a StairMaster.
So I got hot very suddenly and quickly.
It was better than I thought.
The reason was
there had been so many stairs
that were even more terrible.
I was just grateful
that there wasn't any snow.
We have to go up anyway,
so it's great to do it without snow.
It reminded me
of the stairs from hell in Hallasan.
I mean the Stairway to Heaven.
CRACKS UP
When I think about that…
Dowoon and I know what we're both thinking
just by looking at each other.
DOWOON'S POSTURE
IS THE SAME AS IT WAS THEN
Gosh.
Gosh!
Here it comes.
CAR-THE QUICKLY FEELS SOMETHING
SIGHING
Gosh.
YOU CAN GO AHEAD
Go ahead.
MR. NINE MUSES IS THE FIRST
TO TIRE OUT AGAIN TODAY
He must be tired.
THE MEMBERS WAIT FOR HIM
This isn't easy.
HE CATCHES HIS BREATH AND STARTS WALKING
We're going to match your pace,
so move to the front.
Okay.
When I stop, you stop.
Got it.
When you stop, we'll rest.
THEY SET OFF AGAIN
TODAY'S PACEMAKER
The rule of Descend Club
is to match the pace
of the slowest person.
It's our unwritten rule.
And matching Car-the's pace
actually turned out
to be the right choice.
WALKING IN STEP WITH THE PACEMAKER
CHAE-MIN
THOSE FOLLOWING BEHIND
THE CAMERA OPERATORS
AND PRODUCERS WALKING AHEAD
THEY ALL MATCH CAR, THE GARDEN'S PACE
AND TAKE A SLOW HIKE
I got the feeling
that we should match Jung-won's pace
if we wanted to complete
all three peaks together.
It was okay, actually.
We should work as a team.
Can we have a break
to take some layers off?
Sure.
I'm already starting to sweat.
He's lucky. I'm not sweating.
Really?
I'm too cold to sweat.
Walking slowly is much better.
Right?
This time,
I really went at my own pace.
I thought,
"It's fine as long as we go up, right?"
"The production crew
didn't tell me to hurry up either."
The other guys go up fast
because they're energetic.
They even wait for me too.
It's not like anyone is rushing me.
But it'll be a nuisance if I go too slow,
so I thought I should go
at a reasonable and safe pace.
I don't need to walk fast.
I can't.
I can't go.
-I give up.
-You go at your own pace.
ANOTHER PERSON
WHO WALKED UP AT HIS OWN PACE
Is it doable for you guys?
Are you okay?
It's better since I'm walking slowly.
This is slow?
SETTING OFF AGAIN
STILL HIKING SLOWLY
If you go slow, you're invincible.
-What did he say?
-"If you go slow, you're invincible."
If you go slow, you're invincible?
That's right.
"IF YOU GO SLOW, YOU'RE INVINCIBLE"
-YOON SEONG-JUNG
The stairs here are a bit too much.
It's better if you walk slow.
Yes, it's not tiring at all.
Yeah.
NOT TIRED THANKS TO THE PACEMAKER
Once we get past there,
it'll be the end of the stairs.
I don't know if the stairs ending
is a good or bad thing.
We'll find out when we get there.
It's called a scree trail,
which has rocks…
Does it make you worn out and screech?
SCREE TRAIL
SLOPE COMPRISED OF BIG AND SMALL ROCKS
FOOTING IS UNSTABLE SO CAUTION NEEDED
I told you stairs are better.
Stairs are safe at least.
Stairs are simple and repetitive.
I like simple tasks.
THE LONG STRETCH OF STAIRS NEAR AN END
Is that the peak? It looks like one.
THEY'RE NOT AT THE PEAK YET
PEAK 1, GANWOLSAN SUMMIT
CURRENT LOCATION
GANWOLSAN, GANWOLJAE SERVICE AREA,
SINBULSAN, YEONGCHUKSAN
GANWOLSAN 3 KM
3 KM LEFT UNTIL PEAK 1
This is a scree trail.
Watch your ankles.
-Okay.
-Be careful when you step on a rock.
GOING ONTO THE SCREE TRAIL
A SLOPE COMPOSED OF ROCKS AND DIRT
THE SCREE TRAIL CONTINUES ALONG THE RIDGE
The ground feels good here.
The difficulty is rather okay
for a mountain.
-Right?
-Yeah.
The trail we went on before…
Was it because
we only went on difficult trails?
Well, I'm glad there's no snow.
Exactly.
I almost rolled my ankle.
What?
Did you sprain it?
I tweaked it a bit, but it doesn't hurt.
Let's take it slow.
IT'S A GENTLE SLOPE, BUT BE CAREFUL
OF ROCKS ON THE SCREE TRAIL
SINCE IT'S A RIDGE, IT'S VERY WINDY
Goodness.
PUTS ON HIS BALACLAVA
FIGHTING THE HEADWINDS WITH HIS BARE FACE
HE GIVES UP
ZIPS UP AND PERFECTLY BLOCKS OUT THE WIND
DOWOON, TARZZAN, CHAE-MIN, CAR-THE
AS THEY WALK ALONG THE RIDGE
Is that the first peak?
No.
-It is.
-Baenaebong Peak.
They don't count this.
BAENAEBONG HAS AN ELEVATION BELOW 1,000 M
SO IT ISN'T RECOGNIZED
FOR THE COMPLETION CERTIFICATE
THEY ARRIVE AT BAENAEBONG
This is almost 1,000 m
above sea level already.
966 M ABOVE SEA LEVEL
You have 2.6 km left until Ganwolsan.
Where is Ganwolsan?
It's that pointy mountain
you see over there.
They're all pointy though. Hold on.
It's the one you see in front of you.
THEY'RE ALL POINTY
-The one in the middle?
-Yes.
GANWOLSAN SUMMIT
CURRENT LOCATION
-That one?
-Yes.
We need to go all the way there
to complete one peak…
That's so damn high.
FULL OF CONCERNS
So on the way down from the first peak,
there's a place to eat, right?
-Yes.
-That's pretty far though.
Let's just go.
Come on, let's just go.
Well, let's go.
IT WILL TAKE ABOUT 1 HOUR AND 20 MINUTES
TO REACH PEAK 1
CURRENT LOCATION
THEY'LL GO DOWN FROM BAENAEBONG
AND CLIMB BACK UP
DESCENDING FROM BAENAEBONG
I thought we'd come smoothly so far.
-Exactly.
Watch out for the branches.
THE PATH IS SURROUNDED BY SHORT TREES
182 CM TALL
190 CM TALL
177.8 CM TALL
179 CM TALL
THE MEN WITH AN AVERAGE HEIGHT
OF 182.2 CM EVADE THEM WELL
Watch your head.
This area's a bit…
You could scratch your face.
Exactly. Be careful.
THE TUNNEL OF TREE CONTINUES
OUCH
What a difficult path.
THE TOWERING CHAE-MIN ALMOST GOT SCRATCHED
OUCH
TALL PEOPLE AT A DISADVANTAGE
WITH THESE MOUNTAIN FEATURES
This area is a bit adventurous.
Dowoon, your shoelaces are untied.
Thank you.
TIGHTENING THE LACES OF HIS HIKING SHOES
Let's go.
SNIFFS
ACTUALLY, DOWOON'S REAL PROBLEM WAS…
HIS NOSE AND THROAT WERE IN POOR CONDITION
AT THE START OF THE HIKE
Your rhinitis seemed to give you trouble.
Right, my nose.
-It suddenly broke down.
-When did it become like that?
I don't know.
I need to see the footage.
My nose suddenly started to get irritated.
Why is it so downhill now?
We're going down a lot.
That means we need to go up a lot.
HOLLOW LAUGH
NEGATIVE GARDEN: THIS PATH IS SO…
POSITIVE GARDEN: IT'S SO DYNAMIC
I'm behind you, so do worry.
Not "don't worry."
Do worry.
Still,
Car-the must not be too exhausted.
-Me?
-You're talking.
Seeing how I'm yapping?
I can tell by your mouth.
NATTERING WITH CAR, THE GARDEN
ON EASY HIKES
This is how you can enjoy it a bit.
It feels like a hike today.
Yeah, it feels good too.
We need to climb that now.
Yes, what you see there is Ganwoljae.
We're almost there.
We're almost there?
ESTIMATED TO TAKE ABOUT 45 MINUTES
TO GET HERE
He's a complete liar.
A complete lie.
We can clearly see it, so what are you…
Our producer lies…
A lot.
On your left is where we were yesterday
in downtown Ulsan.
We were there yesterday?
It's where we hung out yesterday.
Where did we hang out yesterday?
Yeah, where did we hang out?
LAUGHING
RUNNING AWAY
-We hung out yesterday?
-He's not too sure either.
So he just points and walks away.
Tarzzan, do you see Ulsan on your left?
-Yes.
-Can you tell what area that is?
Of course not.
Really?
What area is that?
EVEN THE ONE FROM ULSAN DOESN'T KNOW
FACT: CAN'T SEE
WHERE THEY HUNG OUT FROM HERE
He's just showed a random area.
Because of the reflection of the light…
-Reflection of the light?
-What?
We can see everything clearly.
DOPAMINE BLAST FROM LAUGHING
LAME EXCUSE
Goodness, it's so windy.
ASCENDING AGAIN
THROUGH THE WIND AND TREES
This mountain is difficult
in a different way.
Right.
The path's rough here.
GOING DOWN ANOTHER ROCK WITH A BIG DROP
Which way do you go?
This must be the highlight of the trail.
TARZZAN USES THE HIKING POLES
DOWOON TAKES BIG STEPS TOO
"MOUNTAINS AND LIFE ALLOW MORE
TO THOSE WHO ARE BRAVE"
MOUNTAINEER UM HONG-GIL
Doesn't it feel like a hard section
will be at the end?
-I think so.
-Yeah.
I think there will be.
ALMOST AT PEAK 1
GRUNTING
SIGHING
MORE SIGHING
What is this place?
FROM TARZZAN'S CAM
This is basically rock climbing.
What's with this place?
SIGHING
PASSING THE TOUGH SECTION AT THE END
The first of three peaks.
Peak One.
Ganwolsan.
THEY ARRIVE AT PEAK 1, GANWOLSAN
-It's beautiful here.
-Yes.
GANWOLSAN
WITH AN ELEVATION OF 1,069 M,
A FAMOUS YEONGNAM ALPS MOUNTAIN
KNOWN FOR THE SILVER GRASS FIELD
"GANWOLJAE"
GANWOLSAN
CURRENT LOCATION
HIKING TO SUMMIT
PEAK 1 GANWOLSAN CONQUERED
-Let's go down now.
-Okay.
Hold on…
I explained yesterday…
-What is it?
-What did you explain?
For every peak…
RUMMAGING
It's a cash prize!
Hey, they're giving us money.
Gosh!
Really?
IN SEOUL BEFORE HIKE
It's a three-peak challenge.
For each peak you reach,
we'll give you a cash prize.
-You'll give us money?
-What?
-Just a little. For team dinners.
-Money?
One envelope for each peak.
We wanted to give you a little bit.
Manager Car, thank you for your efforts.
HANDS OUT FIRST ENVELOPE
FOR CLIMBING PEAK 1
How much is it?
-What?
-It's 40,000 won.
So 10,000 per person.
10,000 WON X 4 = 40,000 WON
LOSING ENERGY
Still, for the team dinner…
Yeah, sure.
SURPRISED BY THE AMOUNT
You'll get one for each peak.
Can you complain for us, Jung-won?
Look.
How long have we been hiking?
An hour and a half?
A bit longer than two hours.
Then, our hourly wage is 5,000 won.
ROUGHLY 5,000 WON AN HOUR
It was worse than not getting paid at all.
"Are they making fun of us?"
How can the wage be 5,000 won per hour
in this day and age?
Back when I had my first part-time job,
it was still more than that.
I'm sorry, but the amount wasn't much,
so it didn't really register.
DISAPPOINTED SIGH
-Minimum wage is…
-We'll hang onto it.
It's still money though.
BOTH PARTIES HAVE A BAD TASTE
IN THEIR MOUTHS
SHOWING OFF
ANYWAYS, FIRST ENVELOPE RECEIVED
THEY DEPART FROM GANWOLSAN'S SUMMIT
Let's go.
HEADING TO GANWOLJAE SERVICE AREA
ABOUT 20 MINUTES AWAY
Is it downhill all the way there?
Yes, it's almost all downhill.
Watch out for your knees and ankles.
THEY'LL CONTINUE ON A GENTLE DOWNHILL
LIKE THE PATH,
THE WIND BECOMES GENTLE TOO
It's warm and then it's cold.
This mountain seems to have mood swings.
Yeah.
THE CHANGING WINDS MAKE IT TOUGH
BUT THE RISE AND FALL OF THE RIDGE
CREATES BEAUTIFUL SCENERY
DOWOON CAPTURES THE VIEW WITH HIS CAMERA
I see stairs over there.
Do you see the brown area down there?
Yes.
That's the silver grass field.
And that's the Ganwoljae Service Area.
We'll have lunch there.
Near the parking lot?
That's right.
It looks very well-maintained.
Yes.
GANWOLJAE SERVICE AREA
This is the biggest silver grass field
in Korea.
Crash Landing on You was here?
This is where they filmed
the paragliding scene.
I remember. In Episode One.
Yes.
Does she paraglide
and end up in North Korea?
This is where they filmed that scene.
SON YE-JIN PARAGLIDED HERE IN THE SHOW
How did they get up here?
A parking lot's over there.
CARS HALFWAY UP A MOUNTAIN
What on earth?
THE PARKING LOT IS USED BY PARK STAFF
ONLY VEHICLES WITH PRIOR AUTHORIZATION
ARE ALLOWED
IT MAKES HIM LOSE ENERGY
There's a parking lot.
Shall we go?
DESCEND CLUB WALKS
TO THE SILVER GRASS FIELD
GANWOLJAE
AT AN ELEVATION OF 900 M
THE PASS CONNECTS GANWOLSAN AND SINBULSAN
MANY HIKERS VISIT TO SEE
THE VAST SILVER GRASS FIELD
A VIEW OF DOWNTOWN ULSAN AND THE OCEAN
The golden silver grass field
stretched out like this.
It was so beautiful and enchanting.
I thought, "I didn't know
there was a place like this in Korea."
I thought it'd be really nice
to capture it on camera.
Later, whether for a TV show or a movie,
I thought it'd be really beautiful
to shoot in a place like this.
It was beautiful.
You come with your family,
and you happily talk
with each other like this while hiking.
As you eat your packed lunches,
you'd go, "The view is amazing, isn't it?"
That would be perfect.
DO YOU REMEMBER COMING HERE
WHEN YOU WERE YOUNG?
I think I vaguely remember it.
I do remember whining.
"How much further do we have to go?"
I remember saying that.
LITTLE LEE CHAE-WON
CLIMBED THE YEONGNAM ALPS
I don't know if it was the same field,
but I do remember that.
It's so beautiful here.
Isn't it beautiful?
Yes.
What?
"Isn't it beautiful?"
"Yes."
He answered his own question.
What do you think? Doesn't it look
like the Alps of Yeongnam?
I don't know.
I don't know what the Alps look like.
How would I know
if this is the Alps of Yeongnam?
But it's definitely different
from the snowy mountains, right?
Yes. It is pretty here.
I feel better here
than I did on snowy trails.
It definitely is the prettiest here.
I agree.
It makes you feel a bit calm.
Being too high up honestly scares me.
The silver grass field is beautiful.
I can see why they shot a TV show here.
Exactly.
It's cool!
It's cool.
Great job, everyone.
That's one peak.
THEY ARRIVE AT GANWOLJAE SERVICE AREA
Peak One, out.
"Peak One, out."
THEY'LL HAVE LUNCH HERE
A PLEASANT INDOOR AREA
IT BECOMES A SHELTER FOR HIKERS
They sell snacks and eggs here.
-I want eggs.
-Me too.
THE SHOP HAS FOOD
FOR SIMPLE MEALS AND SNACKS
CUP NOODLES
2,000 WON
INSTANT RICE
CHOCOLATE BARS
1,000 WON
THEY SELL SIMPLE HIKING ACCESSORIES TOO
I'll get one Shin Ramyun and an egg.
If anyone needs more water,
we can each get another bottle.
THEY EACH TAKE A CUP OF INSTANT NOODLES
Should we use our cash prize?
-Let's do it.
-Okay.
THEY AGREE
PAYS 15,000 WON WITH THEIR CASH PRIZE
The cash prize!
You're using it right away?
Yes, since it offends me.
PURCHASED 4 CUP NOODLES,
4 ROASTED EGGS, AND 1 BOTTLE OF WATER
-Thank you.
-Is this the water?
-Yeah.
A HUGE HOT WATER DISPENSER
A GOOD SUPPLY OF HOT WATER
Shall we eat outside?
THERE ARE OUTDOOR TABLES TOO
The view's pretty nice.
A BEAUTIFUL VIEW
This place is like a park.
It didn't work.
CAR-THE EATS THE EGG AS AN APPETIZER
CHAE-MIN'S APPETIZER IS AN EGG TOO
YUM
THEY INHALE THEIR EARLY LUNCH
SATISFIED
It's good, right?
Ramyeon tastes good in the mountains.
Of all the ramyeon
we've had on mountains so far,
this was cooked best.
This is how it tastes
in the military during marches.
Where on earth did Producer Nah go though?
There he comes.
He's really slow today.
WHAT'S WITH HIM TODAY?
CAN ONLY THROW AWAY GARBAGE AND FOOD WASTE
OF THINGS PURCHASED
AT GANWOLJAE SERVICE AREA
CURRENT TIME
Let's take a group photo and go.
-Okay.
PHOTO TIME IN THE MIDDLE
OF THE SILVER GRASS FIELD
-Okay.
-Nice.
One more time.
Let's brighten our faces and smile.
CAR, THE GARDEN LAUGHS
You look so cheerful, Car-the.
CHEERFUL SMILE
THEY HARMONIOUSLY FINISH
THE GROUP PHOTO SHOOT
GANWOLJAE SERVICE AREA
CURRENT LOCATION
Let's head to the second peak, Sinbulsan.
BEGINNING: STAIRS
MIDDLE: ROCKY SCREE TRAIL
END: RIDGE TRAIL
AFTER SUFFERING COMES THE SCENERY
THE NO PAIN, NO GAIN TRAIL
ABOUT 1 HOUR UNTIL SINBULSAN
11:39 A.M.
DEPARTING GANWOLJAE SERVICE AREA
-It'll take an hour.
-Okay.
-Let's go.
-Go.
BEYOND THE PASS TO SINBULSAN
Sinbulsan
THE ULSAN NATIVE HUMS TO HIMSELF
COUGHING
THE CHANGWON NATIVE COUGHS
THE GYEONGGI AND INCHEON NATIVES
ARE SILENT
LEAD: THE SEONGPANAK TEAM PAIR
TAIL: THE GWANEUMSA TEAM PAIR
THE SINBULSAN HIKING LINEUP SETS OFF
ENTERING THE STAIRS SECTION
THE STAIRS DESCEND CLUB IS CLIMBING
THEY AREN'T VERY STEEP
BUT IT'S LONG AND DOESN'T ALLOW FOR REST
THEY'VE SLOWED DOWN
AFTER EATING AND RESTING
AND THE ADDED PRESSURE
FROM THE FIRST CONSECUTIVE HIKE
RESULTS IN EVERYONE HIKING IN SILENCE
EVERYONE'S STEPS ARE HEAVY
EVERYONE LOOKS EMPTY ON ENERGY
AND THEY TRAVEL OVER THE STAIRS THAT WAY
FOR A VERY LONG TIME
THEY DID NOT SAY A SINGLE WORD
AFTER THE STEEP SCREE TRAIL
Should we rest here?
12:06 P.M.
MIDWAY OBSERVATION DECK
Is that the peak?
Yes.
A SHORT REST WHILE LOOKING
AT THE PEAK OF SINBULSAN
THE YOUNGER MEMBERS
ARE BUSY CHECKING THEIR GEAR
LOOKING AROUND
NEGATIVE GARDEN: I'M SO ANGRY
I'm really angry.
HE WHISPERS HIS COMPLAINTS TO AVOID A FINE
ROAMING AROUND
HE GOES TO A CORNER
SNAP
HE'S TAKING PHOTOS OF THE SCENERY?
36 DAYS AGO
HIKING TRAINING ON HIS OWN ON ACHASAN
But you know what?
I'm not interested in natural scenery.
HIS INDIFFERENCE TO SCENERY
WAS CLEAR FROM THE START
31 DAYS AGO
SEORAKSAN TRAINING CAMP
My problem is,
I'm not interested
-in natural scenery.
-Seriously?
INDIFFERENT ON SEORAKSAN TOO
29 DAYS AGO
HIKING TAEBAEKSAN
This is a yew tree.
Is this show funded by the government?
-Am I right?
-Right?
HE WAS STILL CYNICAL ON TAEBAEKSAN
8 DAYS AGO
HIKING HALLASAN
It's a cedar forest.
I hear it emits a lot of phytoncides.
INHALING
This is all right.
HE SLOWLY STARTED
TO OPEN HIS HEART IN HALLASAN
This looks pretty nice.
HE NATURALLY STARTS TAKING PICTURES
It is pretty cool.
HE EVEN EXPRESSES HIS HEARTFELT THOUGHTS
It is cool.
HE'S SLOWLY OPENING UP
AND SO, HE'S TAKING PHOTOS TODAY TOO
FEIGNING IGNORANCE
It's just for the sake of it.
Did you take pictures of the view?
CAUGHT RIGHT AWAY
Finally.
What's gotten into him?
What?
I mean…
I'll seriously tell you why I took them.
When I tell others
I've been hiking mountains,
they go,
"You probably didn't even
go up that high."
They keep doubting me.
I just want to show them.
HIS EXCUSE GROWS LONG
PERHAPS DUE TO EMBARRASSMENT
We were surprised
to see you taking photos.
Should I compare them for you?
WILLINGLY PROVIDING
DISCUSSION TOPIC IN EXCITEMENT
This is Seoraksan.
"Gosh, isn't it super cool?"
That's the vibe.
That's the vibe for Seoraksan.
-It sure has a rugged vibe.
-Yes, rugged.
"Hey, look at this."
"The crater is so deep. Take a photo."
That's the vibe.
"You're not taking a photo?
It's Baengnokdam!"
That's what it feels like.
But this one?
"Hello."
"It's very relaxing."
"It's not that high."
THE YEONGNAM ALPS' VIEW MADE
EVEN CAR, THE GARDEN'S HEART MELT
Yahoo.
WITH CHEERFUL ENERGY
THEY START WALKING TOWARD SINBULSAN AGAIN
-Hello.
Good luck.
GOOD MANNERS LEARNED FROM HALLASAN
ALONG THE RIDGE WHERE THE WIND HAS SETTLED
On the ridge to the second peak,
the ridge path
was mostly like flat ground.
I didn't even run out of breath
in that area.
It's over there.
Looks like it.
THEY'RE AT EYE-LEVEL
WITH THE SUMMIT OF SINBULSAN
THE DESIRE TO TAKE IN WITH THEIR EYES
THE SCENERY THEY SEE AS THEY WALK ALONG
This is the best mountain.
The path is paved well.
WOODEN STAIRS WITH RUBBER MATS
TO PREVENT SLIPPING
Yeah, this will help you not slip.
Every part of this trail
was made thoughtfully.
YOU SEEMED TO REALLY LIKE
THE YEONGNAM ALPS
The facilities were made
very thoughtfully.
Starting with the restrooms.
They even had rubber mats in place
on the trail at times.
The Yeongnam Alps were outstanding.
Chae-min, what did I say mountains
overlapping like that were called?
Sorry?
It's when you see
layers and layers of mountains.
You said that before?
Pork belly layer mountains.
Does anyone remember?
You said that?
You didn't. You just made it up.
I explained it twice on Taebaeksan.
THE ANSWER IS
Sangeurime.
We've never heard of it before.
THEY JUST WANT TO KEEP GOING
-You never told us.
-We've never heard of it before.
The mountains you see beyond mountains
are called sangeurime.
"San?"
Sangeurime. It's a pure Korean word.
EVERYONE HAS FORGOTTEN
THE MEMORY OF TAEBAEKSAN
SANGEURIME OR MOUNTAIN SILHOUETTE
THE FAINT VIEW OF DISTANT MOUNTAINS
LINED UP IN LAYERS LIKE SHADOWS
THEY DON'T RECALL AND WALK
WITH SANGEURIME IN THE BACKGROUND
CLOSE TO THE SUMMIT OF SINBULSAN
We're almost there.
We're at the second peak now?
I guess they'll give us money again.
Right, the money.
THE SECOND CASH PRIZE
IS WAITING AT THE PEAK
Shall we run to the destination?
Go ahead.
HE SUDDENLY STARTS RUNNING ON THE TRAIL
Models are on another level.
THE MODEL ARRIVES
Why did you suddenly run?
I thought it'd be nice
to have a clip of me running.
HE'S BECOME A TRUE ENTERTAINER NOW
You still have stamina left.
Car-the is flying.
Are you flying?
-Balance.
-He's showing a lot of emotions today.
I'm balancing myself.
HE FLIES TO THE DESTINATION
Dowoon, wasn't this how Hallasan felt?
We came all that way,
but they said
we'd only gone a third of the way.
ENDLESS HIKING IS DÉJÀ VU
FOR GWANEUMSA TEAM
-Hallasan?
-Yes.
This is so much better than Hallasan.
Of course.
THEY ALL ARRIVE
This is sick.
APPROACHING THE TOWER OF STONES
THEY'D ONLY SEEN FROM AFAR
This is nice.
You're so handsome!
I don't know who you are,
but you're handsome.
Am I handsome?
No.
Not me?
No, you're cool!
Am I cool?
FINE, ALREADY
You're pretty too, ma'am.
Sure, thanks.
Hey, look at that guy.
THAT GUY IS SMILING
She said I'm not handsome.
WHAT HAPPENED?
-She said no.
-You look macho.
Well,
I guess she wanted to gaze
at some handsome men.
Since the mountains are rough,
I think she wanted to cleanse her eyes
with handsome men
rather than someone like me.
She said, "He's handsome!"
So I said, "Aren't I handsome?"
And she said, "No!"
"What?"
HURT
"No"?
She had clear standards.
Ulsan has clear standards.
Actually, I rather liked that.
It's better than those
forcing themselves to say it.
Honestly, I know it too.
If they say I'm very handsome,
I go, "You're lying."
Congratulations.
Good job, everyone.
That's two out of three peaks!
THEY ARRIVE AT PEAK 2, SINBULSAN
SINBULSAN
ELEVATION OF 1,159 M
TALLEST OF 3 PEAKS
IN TOP 100 MOUNTAINS OF KOREA
ALSO ITS SILVER GRASS FIELD
IS IN THE TWELVE SCENIC PLACES OF ULSAN
SINBULSAN
HIKING TO SUMMIT
PEAK 2 SINBULSAN CONQUERED
HANDS OUT SECOND ENVELOPE
FOR CLIMBING PEAK 2
Open it.
You have to give us
20,000 won each this time.
WISHING FOR DOUBLE THE AMOUNT FOR PEAK 2
HOW MUCH IS THE SECOND CASH PRIZE?
Peak Two.
SECOND CASH PRIZE
40,000 WON
THEIR REACTIONS ARE AS FROZEN
AS THEIR WAGES
TRUDGING
EXCITED WITHOUT KNOWING WHAT'S GOING ON
They're cheering you on back there.
A WAVE OF SUPPORT FOR THE FROZEN WAGES?
Lastly, the third peak.
-Where is it?
-Look over there.
In the middle to the left,
one looks a bit like a cliff.
That's on Yeongchuksan,
our third and final peak.
-That cliff?
-Yes.
Once you get to Yeongchuksan,
you will have conquered
three peaks of the Yeongnam Alps.
CURRENT LOCATION
TO THE FINAL DESTINATION, YEONGCHUKSAN
IT STARTS WITH A DESCENT
BELOW IS THE SILVER GRASS PLATEAU,
SINBULJAE
ONCE THEY PASS SINBULJAE
THEY'LL ENCOUNTER A LONG STRETCH OF RIDGE
AFTER CLIMBING UP AND DOWN THE RIDGE
A ROUGH ROCKY PATH SIGNALS END
YOU CAN'T LET YOUR GUARD DOWN
THE TRAIL TO END
TODAY'S CONSECUTIVE HIKES ON A HIGH NOTE
THEY DEPART FROM SINBULSAN'S SUMMIT
You're so handsome.
Thank you.
THE FIRST TO ANSWER GETS THE COMPLIMENT
You're so handsome.
Thank you.
THE ACTUAL COMPLIMENT TARGET
ISN'T BOTHERED BY THE STEAL
I'm so glad the weather is nice.
RESUMING HIKING HAPPILY
I'm really happy.
LEAD: THE SEONGPANAK TEAM PAIR AGAIN
TAIL: THE GWANEUMSA TEAM PAIR AGAIN
THEY HEAD TOWARD SINBULJAE
WITH THEIR HALLASAN PARTNERS
IT STARTS WITH A ROCKY PATH
ON A GENTLE SLOPE
ALONG THE WOODEN STAIRS
GOING DOWN FOR 20 MINUTES STRAIGHT
It's nice here.
The trail is easy now.
FROM DOWOON'S CAM
ENJOYING THE VIEW WHILE WALKING
SEARCHING
YOON DORAEMON TAKES OUT
SOMETHING FROM HIS POCKET
HE TRIES HARD TO PEEL IT AS HE WALKS DOWN
HIS FAVORITE TRAIL FOOD,
SWEET RED BEAN JELLY
PRECIOUS TO HIM
A BITE OF SWEET RED BEAN JELLY
TO REFUEL ENERGY
ANOTHER BITE
THIRD BITE
REFUELING FINISHED IN THREE BITES
HE PUTS THE TRASH BACK IN HIS POCKET
HE WALKS ON AFTER RECHARGING
It's a dog!
HE SPOTS A DOG HIKING
HARD FOR A DOG LOVER TO JUST PASS BY
AS STILL AS A STONE WHILE WATCHING THE DOG
AFTER BEING COMFORTED
BY THE DOG, HE RETURNS
HIS RHINITIS IS STILL THERE
I haven't been sweating much
because the wind keeps blowing.
Right.
As I sweat, it just cools.
AFTER WALKING ALONG WITH THE COOL BREEZE
THEY EVENTUALLY ARRIVE AT THIS PLACE
A PATH WHERE THE WIND PASSES THROUGH
THE SILVER GRASS PLATEAU
WHERE FOUR ROADS MEET
THEY ARRIVE AT SINBULJAE
SNIFFLING
-Dowoon.
-Yes?
-Are you okay?
-I think I have a head cold.
Did you catch a cold?
Maybe? My nose is so itchy.
Do you have allergies?
No, not that I know of.
I think you have allergies, Dowoon.
Really?
You're allergic to mountains.
DIAGNOSIS COMPLETE
Anyway, we can make it
to the third and final peak in an hour.
Okay, let's speed up for the homestretch.
AWAKENED BY THE NEWS
THAT THERE'S ONLY 1 HOUR LEFT TO GO
Okay, everyone. Make sure to follow along.
Let's move out.
ENERGY IS GOOD
Let's see how tough
the Gwaneumsa trail was.
Okay, I'll go really fast.
SEONGPANAK TEAM'S PROVOCATION
FIRES HIM UP
I need to run to get it out of my system.
Here we go.
LEAVING SINBULJAE AFTER A REST
LEAD: AN AWAKENED DOWOON
MIDDLE: TARZZAN ALSO PICKS UP THE PACE
TAIL: CAR, THE GARDEN AND CHAE-MIN
MINISTER OF TRANSPORT'S NOSE
HAS SLIGHTLY CLEARED
You're getting in my way.
OVERCOMES HIS MOUNTAIN ALLERGY
AND GOES FULL THROTTLE ON THE STAIRS
CURRENT LOCATION
Let me know anytime you need trail food.
THE MINISTER OF TRANSPORT IS IN CHARGE
OF THEIR TRAIL FOOD AGAIN TODAY
I want spaghetti.
I don't have that.
GOING DOWNHILL AGAIN
It's 1.4 km?
Yes, the summit of Yeongchuksan
is 1.4 km away.
TOWARD THE FINAL AND THIRD PEAK
THEY CLIMB THE RIDGE HIGH IN THE CLOUDS
FAR OFF IN THE DISTANCE
LOOKING AT THE SUMMIT AS THEY GO
Gosh, this is practically a cliff.
DOCENT: DO YOU SEE THAT OVER THERE?
You can see
the starting point of the mountain.
Sorry?
Isn't it cool?
What is?
We came from there…
What? Don't leave.
ESCAPES
Wait for us.
Wait for us!
I'll go first.
EX-DOCENT: I WON'T EXPLAIN ANYMORE
We were going at a good pace.
Exactly.
You know what I think?
I think I'm allergic to his talks.
My nose keeps running.
That's exactly it.
That's it.
This is crazy.
BEHIND THE YOUNGER MEMBERS IN THE LEAD
AND ALBEIT A BIT SLOW,
HE SEEMED TO KEEP UP WELL
LEAD: TARZZAN
MIDDLE 1: DOWOON
MIDDLE 2: CHAE-MIN
ALL THE WAY AT THE TAIL: CAR, THE GARDEN
Car-the.
THEY FINALLY SPOT HIM NOW
Man, I'm in such a bad mood.
THE PACEMAKER CAN ONLY FOLLOW THEIR PACE
Let's go.
We should let Car-the go first.
All right.
Let's match his pace.
Take it slow.
THE PACEMAKER FINALLY RETURNS TO HIS PLACE
There's a lesson to learn from hiking.
-What?
-Hiking teaches a lesson.
HE HAD TIME TO CONTEMPLATE WHILE FOLLOWING
You have to go at your own pace.
"GO AT YOUR OWN PACE"
SINGER CAR, THE GARDEN
APPLYING THE LESSON LEARNED TODAY
So maybe, you know,
Producer Nah is doing it right.
Walking slowly…
Then, I want to rest.
And falling behind.
That actually was the answer.
NOT SURE IF THAT'S A COMPLIMENT OR NOT
He's doing it right.
By the way, where's Producer Nah?
I think he's way behind us.
No, I think he took a car down
from that rest stop earlier.
WITH QUESTIONS OF PRODUCER NAH'S
UNKNOWN WHEREABOUTS
We have the final 300 m left.
EXCITED HOOTS
YEONGCHUKSAN 0.3 KM
THEY HAPPILY PASS THE 0.3 KM SIGN
AS SOON AS THEY PASS BY,
AN UPHILL SCREE TRAIL APPEARS
FOR THE FIRST TIME IN A WHILE
TO INDICATE THE START OF THIS ROAD
A RIDGE WITH A GENTLE SLOPE
A SMOOTH SILVER GRASS ROAD
NONE OF THOSE ARE PRESENT HERE
THE START OF THE CRUX
RIGHT BEFORE THE THIRD PEAK
THE FINAL SPURT TO PEAK 3
5 HOURS AND 21 MINUTES HAVE PASSED
I was running out of stamina
during the last climb.
I felt the adversity.
It was all rocks.
ROCKS
EXHALING
AFTER ONLY WALKING
ON DIRT AND WOODEN STAIRS FOR A BIT
EXHALING
ESPECIALLY WHEN THEIR FEET TOUCH
THE GROUND, THEY FEEL MORE FATIGUED
IT ISN'T EASY TO SPEED UP
SHAKING HIS HEAD
THE SUMMIT SEEMS SO CLOSE YET IT'S SO FAR
Goodness.
SIGHING
ON THE VERGE OF RUNNING OUT OF STAMINA
THEY ARRIVE
JUST A FEW STEPS AWAY FROM THE PEAK
What is this?
It's a cliff.
We'll need to use our hands…
THE SLOPE IS PRETTY MUCH
LIKE THAT OF ROCK CLIMBING
ONCE THEY CLIMB THE FINAL CLIFF
-It's on your right.
-We've arrived at Yeongchuksan!
THEY ARRIVE AT PEAK 3, YEONGCHUKSAN
Good job, everyone.
Well done!
-Well done, everyone.
-Great job.
We're in Yangsan now.
YEONGCHUKSAN
CONNECTS TO GANWOLSAN AND SINBULSAN
THE FINAL PEAK OF THE CHALLENGE
TONGDOSA TEMPLE IS LOCATED HERE
The Yeongnam Alps' three-peak challenge.
You did it!
THE YEONGNAM ALPS' 3-PEAK CHALLENGE
COMPLETE
Let's sit down.
PLOPPING DOWN AS SOON AS THEY ARRIVE
You secured a great spot.
Just nice.
GOT HIS STONE BED
THIRD CASH PRIZE
-Manager Car.
-I'm beat.
Thank you.
HANDS OUT THIRD ENVELOPE
FOR CLIMBING PEAK 3
Will the final one have more money?
-A bonus?
-Right.
What?
There's more!
HOPEFUL
-It's 80,000 won.
-So, 20,000 each.
Nice.
-Thank you.
-No problem.
Thank you.
-President Tar.
-Yes?
When we planned the hike yesterday,
you promised to talk about
how you felt about hiking for one minute.
-Right.
-What?
You planned that last night.
Wasn't that saying goodbye to the viewers
since it's the last mountain?
FINAL APPROVER SUDDENLY CHANGES
Yeah, the final episode.
The Yeongnam Alps
were designed very thoughtfully.
They have good stairs.
It's a mountain that's easy to hike.
Ulsan is good.
-Ulsan is good.
-Right?
REMARKS THAT MAKE
THE ULSAN NATIVE PROUD
CAN'T FORGET THE SUMMIT PHOTO
YEONGCHUKSAN
Here we go. Let's smile a bit.
One, two, three.
THE OLDER MEMBERS ARE OBEDIENT
Why? Why do you hike?
THE YOUNGER MEMBERS POSE ON THEIR OWN
I think I look pretty sexy.
Pretend you're looking far away.
SUGGESTING A NEW POSE
THEY UNDERSTAND RIGHT AWAY NOW
A PHOTO TAKEN
WHILE LOOKING AT THE FOOTHILLS
Let's go!
FINISHING WITH THEIR SIGNATURE POSE
FEBRUARY 12, 2026, THE YEONGNAM ALPS'
3-PEAK CHALLENGE IS COMPLETE
YEONGCHUKSAN
HIKING TO SUMMIT
PEAK 3, YEONGCHUKSAN CONQUERED
THE YEONGNAM ALPS' 3-PEAK CHALLENGE
COMPLETE
THEY START TO DESCEND
We'll walk down slowly.
Let's go.
TODAY'S DESCENDING TRAIL
YEONGCHUKSAN
Let's go to Jinae Village.
DESCEND TO JINAE VILLAGE
ABOUT 6 KM
YEONGCHUKSAN
ALONG THE STEEP RIDGE
THE SCREE TRAIL CONTINUES IN THIS SECTION
THE STAFF'S PICK
THE FINAL CRUX
GROANING
This isn't easy.
ROUGH FROM THE START
It's very steep.
FROM CHAE-MIN'S CAM
Watch out.
Damn.
Why is it so slippery here?
The path is not good here.
ASCENDING IS TOUGH,
AND DESCENDING IS DANGEROUS
Jung-won.
No, I'm just testing it.
Testing the ground.
HE THOROUGHLY TESTS IT FIRST
A HIKING CLUB
THAT SPECIALIZES IN DESCENDING
DESCEND CLUB
HISTORY OF DESCENTS
HUIUNGAK SHELTER, SEORAKSAN
JANGGUNBONG, TAEBAEKSAN
BAENGNOKDAM, HALLASAN
THEY DESCENDED TOP-TIER MOUNTAINS
Things can't be worse than Seoraksan.
And we hiked that one.
USING ALL THE DESCENT TIPS AND TRICKS
THEY'VE LEARNED SO FAR
TIP 1: USE LONG POLES
TIP 2: TAKE SHORT STRIDES
TIP 3: BEND YOUR KNEES
AND LOWER YOUR CENTER OF GRAVITY
TIP 4: REPLENISH YOUR ENERGY OFTEN
WITH TRAIL FOOD
DESCENDING STEEP SLOPES
IS A PIECE OF CAKE NOW
HUMMING
TIP 5: KEEP YOUR MIND AT EASE
WERE YOU FEELING HAPPY ON YOUR WAY DOWN?
Honestly, the Yeongnam Alps were fine.
I wasn't going to admit it.
Honestly, they're good mountains.
GOOD MOUNTAIN GARDEN'S POSTURE
HAS RELAXED TOO
Car-the seemed to have some stamina left.
I thought it was
the perfect trail for him.
YEONGCHUKSAN
CURRENT LOCATION
THE ROUGH TERRAIN ENDS
It's nice here.
I hope all the paths are like this.
Me too.
NOW THEY DESCEND
THE GENTLE FOREST PATH
It'd be nice if this path continues.
It's beautiful.
I hope it continues.
-This really feels like a hiking trail.
-A walking trail.
THE FIRST PLEASANT DESCENT IN A WHILE
I can't believe he ran away.
He's unbelievable.
SOMEONE IS NOWHERE TO BE SEEN
-Jung-won.
-Yeah?
You know Yung-suk ran off, right?
Yeah. When did he leave?
At the peak, we kept waiting…
We rested for a long time too.
NOW CERTAIN HE RAN AWAY
But he still didn't come.
So, I'm pretty sure he went down
from where we had lunch.
I heard something was wrong
with the probiotics he took.
He can't still be in the toilet, can he?
It'd be funny if he was.
ABOUT 3 HOURS AGO
GANWOLJAE SERVICE AREA
I think it's time for me to quit now.
There might be issues with poop.
I was in danger twice.
PRODUCER NAH DESCENDS
FROM GANWOLJAE SERVICE AREA
I feel so angry all of a sudden.
-He's a nongtti.
-Nongtti.
He's a nongtti.
NONGTTI MEANS SHIRKER
IN GYEONGSANG DIALECT
I mean, after he took
our badges like that yesterday…
Exactly.
VERY REPREHENSIBLE
I've never seen him
say anything like that before.
HOW DID YOU FEEL
WHEN PRODUCER NAH DISAPPEARED?
Of course, I felt very exhausted.
Whenever I look back,
he always makes me think,
"I'm doing all right."
But when he wasn't there…
Actually, I looked behind very often.
I always checked if he was coming or not.
At some point,
we didn't see him climbing up.
So…
I realized he abandoned us.
THE ABANDONED MEMBERS
GROANING
Your car could drive up here.
It easily could.
Just say the word.
It'd be cool to rev up here.
Exactly.
I probably shouldn't rev up
and run now, right?
As long as your legs are fine, try it.
-Should I?
-We can't catch you.
HE CLEARS HIS NOSE A BIT
-Careful.
SPRINTING AT TOP SPEED
FROM DOWOON'S CAM
SPEED BEFITTING OF HIS TITLE,
THE MINISTER OF TRANSPORT
THE FASTEST DESCENT
Why did he suddenly go crazy like that?
HE ARRIVES AT THE TRAIL EXIT
Thank you for running with me.
EX-SPECIAL FORCES CAMERAMAN
Damn.
It's better to come down quickly.
Exactly.
I'll save you guys.
THESE THREE ARE STILL DESCENDING
There's always an end. I feel that.
Eventually, it will end.
THE MINISTER OF TRANSPORT
IS ON HIS WAY TO FINISH THEIR DESCENT
They're going to be so happy.
They're going to be so happy!
HE LOOKS THE HAPPIEST
We're almost there now.
Past the alley here…
Nice.
DESCENT ALMOST DONE
-It's over.
-We just need to go straight.
A CAR ENTERS THE TRAIL EXIT
-Gosh.
-Isn't that Dowoon?
He's here. He came to pick us up.
I'm here!
CHEERING
You did it, Dowoon!
You did it.
I don't abandon people!
FOR THE CAR'S ENTRY INTO THE FOREST ROAD
PERMISSION WAS RECEIVED IN ADVANCE
FROM YANGSAN CITY HALL
AFTER 2 HOURS,
ALL MEMBERS COMPLETE DESCENT
How was it?
THOUGHTS ON TODAY'S HIKE?
Honestly, this time,
the show chose a good location.
For the first time, I'm grateful
to the production crew.
If you put in a little bit of effort,
there's so much you can see.
If I find a partner someday,
I want to climb here with them
and show it off.
"Have you seen Crash Landing on You?"
Well, I talked with Car-the,
and he really liked it.
He liked the mountains in my hometown,
and that made me feel happy too.
Yes.
Do you now have an idea
of why people hike?
You gave us a badge
after hiking Seoraksan.
We kept getting them,
and every time I'd put
a new one on my bag,
I felt proud of myself.
Once the bag eventually fills up,
it'll feel like I've become
a professional mountaineer.
I felt that psychological sense of reward.
TAKE A HIKE!
THEY GRADUALLY COLLECTED
THE REASONS TO HIKE
When you hike,
it's definitely nice
to show off to your friends.
When you walk up stairs
and your friend's suffering,
you can tell them,
"Come on, man. This is nothing."
"I've climbed whole mountains."
It's good for nagging.
I have something to brag about now.
My answer will be the same until the end.
I still don't know why people hike.
At least Car-the has changed.
I think it's a big change.
Do you have an idea now
of why people hike?
No.
Honestly, the emotions I felt
on the Yeongnam Alps yesterday?
I can feel that at Mangwon Hangang Park.
WHY ON EARTH DO PEOPLE HIKE?
I DON'T KNOW
I'm serious.
Yes, you can definitely feel
the same feelings there too.
I still don't know if climbing's worth it.
I have no idea.
STILL DOESN'T KNOW WHY PEOPLE HIKE
SEORAKSAN, TAEBAEKSAN, HALLASAN
YEONGNAM ALPS' 3-PEAK CHALLENGE
Good job, everyone.
Well done, guys. Seriously.
VERY EXHAUSTED
Let's go eat some meat.
HEADING TO DINNER
JINMI BULGOGI
DESCEND CLUB'S DESTINATION
AN EONYANG BULGOGI RESTAURANT
THAT LURES YOU IN WITH ITS SMELL
WELL-HEATED CHARCOAL FIRE
GRILLED FLAT-PRESSED BEEF
EONYANG BULGOGI,
THE SIGNATURE DISH OF EONYANG, ULSAN
THE SIDES ADD TO THE SAVORY FLAVORS
A GENEROUSLY PREPARED FULL SPREAD
DESCEND CLUB ARRIVES
-Thank you.
-We're here.
Let's eat.
-Let's eat.
-I'm so hungry.
GETTING OUT QUICKLY
WORN OUT
What?
-Producer Nah! What happened?
-Producer Nah.
-We caught him in the act.
-What did I do wrong? What is it?
Chae-min, why are you so angry?
Why are you so mad?
Where were you earlier?
Hey, I thought we were friends.
ANOTHER ANGRY PERSON
You got changed too.
We heard some stuff about probiotics.
Probiotics?
Let's go inside first.
The tough thing was…
Gosh, your face is so sunburned.
What?
Today…
It was so tough today.
Look at how burned he is!
WHINING
LET'S EAT FIRST
-I'm hungry.
-This way, please.
We'll enjoy the food a bit first.
It's delicious.
RICE PAIRED WITH BULGOGI
This tastes better
if you don't cook it to a crisp.
Really?
The bulgogi is held together.
Ordinary beef bulgogi
has onions and so on.
THE ULSAN DOCENT
It's so good.
This is yours, right?
It's mine.
CHOPSTICKS MOVE INVOLUNTARILY
LIKE BREATHING
You finished one order already?
THE GRILL IS EMPTY NOW
Just a moment.
Thank you. It's delicious, sir.
Please enjoy your food.
REFILLED
This place was on Food Travel too.
A PIECE OF MEAT
A BITE OF RICE
QUICKLY FINISHES A BOWL OF RICE
THE BULGOGI DISAPPEARS
AS FAST AS THEY DESCENT
TWO ORDERS FINISHED
Could you order one more for us?
Thank you.
REFILLED AGAIN
Hyun-yong's the only one
who takes care of us.
Each meal I've had after descending
with Producer Nah has tasted amazing.
But today,
it doesn't taste as good.
THIRD ORDER OF MEAT
SECOND BOWL OF RICE
Whatever the reason was,
it's a bit disappointing.
Because if he had at least told us…
We were so worried.
We were always in the same boat,
so it was okay.
LAUGHING
Since when did you guys
care so much about me?
When we were on the last summit,
we waited for 20 minutes.
Yeah, and I relied on you.
"When will Producer Nah come?"
You guys don't stay on summits for long.
But we stayed there for a while today.
We even took pictures.
IS PRODUCER NAH COMING?
WHERE DID PRODUCER NAH GO?
I think of you like my father.
Dad.
-Dad, what happened?
-Son.
First off, you guys went through a lot.
And so did I.
We all went through a lot,
so let's give ourselves a hand.
ALREADY SULKING
WHATEVER
FAILED TO LIFT THE MOOD
What kind of grown-up
has diarrhea like a kid?
If I were the leader,
I would've at least worn diapers.
How can you wear diapers on the trail?
I would've worn them if they sold any.
Had you told us earlier,
we would've bought them beforehand.
Exactly.
THEY DON'T BUY HIS EXCUSE
THE PRODUCER AND DOCENT
PASSES THE BEEF TARTARE
Thank you, sir!
Thank you, Hyun-yong.
Thank you for the beef tartare.
BLATANT WARM RESPONSE
Hyun-yong really is a decent guy.
He's the real deal.
He has a big heart, and he's cool.
We share each other's pain.
And he must've had it the hardest.
He's always in the lead
because he has to stand behind the camera.
I'm tearing up.
I'm about to cry.
-Are you okay?
-Geez.
Let's do an acrostic poem
with "Park Hyun-yong" later.
GROUP OF NAH YUNG-SUK HATERS FORMED
He's my dear junior colleague too.
And we're all on the same team.
Hey, don't you hear
some kind of strange toilet sound?
PRODUCER NAH ON THE DEFENSIVE
No?
I should go take a dump.
Excuse me.
DOWOON LEAVES HIS SEAT FOR A MOMENT
QUIETLY
Excuse me, Car-the.
I bought these mandu
while thinking of you.
You can have these all by yourself.
You want to drive us further away?
WHAT IS HAPPENING?
It's because he likes mandu.
I thought of him.
VERY SUSPICIOUS
Don't let it slide like this…
If you do…
What kind of mandu are these?
MANDU ALREADY ACCEPTED
I put a little something
in with the mandu.
I got 5 km with the mandu.
ACCUMULATED KM BADGES
I'm fine,
but I don't know about Chae-min.
There was a father-like figure
who always watched
with gentle eyes from behind us.
All I can say is that he abandoned us.
You're right.
Chae-min, you look thirsty though.
Take a cup of Coke.
PRODUCER NAH HANDS HIM COKE
Chae-min doesn't like Coke.
It's good Coke. Have a sip.
-I only drink Sprite.
-Chae-min only drinks Sprite.
There are two cups. How strange.
LAUGHING
Chae-min, I'm asking just in case.
How do you feel about me
not going with you today?
What?
GRINNING FROM EAR TO EAR
I'm sure Producer Nah
didn't do it intentionally.
-Jung-won…
-You should stop too.
-You little brat.
-I want to join too.
That does it, Producer Nah!
CHAOS
ONLY ONE LEFT OUT
He has his reasons, you know!
Producer Nah, this won't do!
I believe you should have
respect for elders.
Of course, up to this point…
Look at him.
I acted too rudely
to someone older than me.
Yeah, watch your emotions.
Well…
CHECKS RIGHT AWAY
Goodness.
Father.
How was your meal?
Yeah.
We're not strangers with Producer Nah.
ACCUMULATED KM BADGES
No, I apologize for my stomach.
-No!
-I apologize.
Come on.
Let's not argue over this.
No, I'm sorry. Chae-min.
I mean, how can you hike if you're sick?
Gosh, I'm tearing up.
TEARY-EYED
Thank you so much.
Seriously…
I'm so sorry.
-I didn't mean to do this.
-I'll go back up.
No.
-You don't have to.
-Come, now.
We only care about your health, Father.
-Then, we'll all forget about it.
-Yes.
THEY COME TO A DRAMATIC AGREEMENT
Congratulations on climbing
the three peaks.
Gosh.
I was just worried, you know.
Well, I felt really bad about it.
When we were criticizing you earlier,
we felt bad.
You know, right?
Of course, I felt it, but…
You don't hate
Producer Nah that much, right?
DOWOON RETURNS WITH NO IDEA
-Right?
-Well, what can you do?
We all made up like grown men.
I see.
We were dragging it out for too long.
Yeah, you shouldn't hate people too much.
HOLDS NO GRUDGES
ACCUMULATED KM BADGES
I didn't think this would be so exciting.
TIME FOR YEONGNAM ALPS BADGES
You're excited?
The Yeongnam Alps' three-peak challenge.
Congratulations.
QUEST COMPLETION BADGES
How many km is it?
Thank you.
Your commemorative badges.
I'm guessing it should be 16 or 17 km?
PEAK 1
GANWOLSAN
SINBULSAN
PEAK 2
YEONGCHUKSAN
PEAK 3
You have earned 16 km per person.
YEONGNAM ALPS' 3 PEAKS
16 KM ROUND TRIP
We said we'd give you something
if you passed 50 km.
-Gold.
-Gold worth three million won.
We made them with 15 g of gold.
-You did?
-We each get 3.75 g?
Each person will get 3.75 g.
They're gold badges.
You're really giving them?
PURE GOLD
3.75 G
WE'RE REALLY GIVING THEM TO YOU
I'll announce the total accumulated km
for each of you.
Car, the garden.
Yes?
You've earned 60 km.
5 KM FROM SECRET DEAL
GENTLE
Tell us how you feel.
"The Mountain and Me."
EMOTIONAL THOUGHTS BEFITTING
A BALLAD SINGER
"The Mountain and Me."
In this world comprised of only these two,
I, the singer Car, the garden,
promise to become someone
who will walk side by side
with the mountains.
ENJOYING A GOOD SHOW
Next.
It's our Minister of Foreign Affairs.
Lee Chae-min.
You've earned 60 km.
5 KM FROM SECRET DEAL
Please give us a few words, Minister.
At this young age…
LEE CHAE-MIN, AGE 27
…I managed to cover
a long distance of 60 km.
I first would like to thank my father.
With…
With this opportunity you gave me,
I was able to learn about life.
Since I've come this far,
I thought about achieving 100 km
for a moment.
But it's not something that can happen
based solely on what I think.
ONE PERSON IS ESPECIALLY SHOCKED
I'll quietly and diligently try my best.
Thank you.
PRODUCTION-FRIENDLY
MINISTER OF FOREIGN AFFAIRS
Anyway, you two earned 60 km.
THE SEONGPANAK TEAM FINISH THEIR REMARKS
Next, Tarzzan.
The president.
You've earned 59 km.
5 KM FROM SECRET DEAL
President Tar, tell us how you feel.
As the president of Descend Club,
it's been an honor to climb
incredible mountains
with such good members.
And my name is Tarzzan.
When you mention "Tarzzan,"
you think of mountains, and vice-versa.
I'll make sure we reach 100 km.
Everyone is…
We should talk about it.
I promise to be a president
who listens to his fellow members.
So, Tarzzan earned 59 km.
Lastly, the Minister of Transport.
Dowoon.
You've earned 54 km.
What a shame.
Still, let's give him a hand.
Why?
But why?
BECAUSE…
HE HAD NO SECRET DEAL
-That's how the cookie crumbles.
-What you can do?
I'm sure they calculated accurately.
They wouldn't get the math wrong.
Shouldn't I be at 59 km too?
FRUSTRATED
BOGUS ARGUMENTS CONTINUES
Once you climb, the distances can differ.
That's nonsense.
Hey, this is ridiculous.
Something must've happened.
Something happened.
FEIGNING IGNORANCE
Tell us how you feel first.
-Tell us how you feel.
-54 km is amazing too.
I've only seen the ocean my whole life.
But I got the chance
to hike mountains
while surrounded
by such wonderful and famous members,
and that was really great.
I don't know how long we'll be together.
Come on! Don't try to run away again.
SOCIAL DISTANCING
I don't know how long we'll be together,
but I'll do my best until the end.
I'll hand out the gold badges now.
Hold on. Why am I at 54 km?
Please explain this to me.
That was according to our calculations.
But there could've been a mistake.
So, I'll ask the three of you.
Was our calculation of 54 km wrong?
There was no error.
Really?
It's true.
Car-the might think differently.
No, it's true.
You jerks made a deal while I was away!
I hurried my way down
and gave all of you rides!
-You little…
-Dowoon.
I thought highly of you!
FURIOUS
Hear me out.
What's there to make a deal for?
CALM DOWN
There's nothing.
This is their job.
They wouldn't make mistakes calculating.
He's right.
ALREADY FULL OF DISTRUST
You know, Dowoon,
I kept refusing to take it.
JUNG-WON…
You got extra km and kept your mouth shut.
But what about me?
Seriously.
You guys are some weird people.
I drove four hours to get here.
FEELING BETRAYED
Still, despite being your first time
hiking these mountains,
you have already hit 50 km.
GOLD BADGES AWARDED
Congratulations. They're real gold badges.
IMPRESSED
WHILE THEY EACH CHECK OUT
THEIR GOLD BADGES
Dowoon.
-Thank you so much for driving.
-Dowoon.
We put in something small too.
GOLD BADGE AWARDED SEPARATELY TO HIM
There we go.
DOWOON GETS AN EXTRA 5 KM TOO
It turns out they're good people.
ACCUMULATED KM BADGES
He takes responsibility.
You've worked so hard
on your quests so far.
Only the last quest remains.
We will reveal the final quest.
The final quest is…
Climbing this is the final quest.
-Yeah.
-Congratulations!
I saw it coming.
Yeah, I knew this would happen.
I was wondering why
it hadn't shown up yet.
FOR THE FIRST TIME ON TAKE A HIKE!
Let's not shoot it.
Yeah, that may be better.
It's dangerous here.
One, two, three.
THEY GIVE UP FILMING
HALFWAY INTO THE FINAL QUEST
It was a lot harder
than the other mountains.
It was a bit…
I mean, what do you want me to do?
What do you want from me?
That section had no mercy.
That place…
Geez!
This was the hardest one for me.
-Harder than Seoraksan?
-Yes.
I don't know why.
This place was the worst.
It was just…
No joke. This place is…
a ********.
Forget about hiking. It's a ********.
Seriously.
I have nothing else to say.
BEFORE THE FINAL QUEST
-Jeotgal.
-Wrong!
DESCEND CLUB'S SECOND ACTIVITY
Hotdog!
Bale.
Wrong!
THE SAME OLD KIM UI-HAN
-There's Santa Claus.
-Wrong!
AND ZZAN OF TAR
Hey, come on!
Three, two…
Gets bigger!
Wrong!
MINISTER OF FOREIGN AFFAIRS'
UNEXPECTED PERFORMANCE
Could you make sure to edit this?
I think it's going to look bad.
Correct!
THE LAST GAME WITH KM ON THE LINE
THE UNEXPECTED REBELLION OF DESCEND CLUB
We'll go home now!
Then, what happens?
CALCULATIONS GET COMPLICATED
It's been a while since I've gone all in.
We're over 100.
-We're over 100. We went over 100!
-Hold on!
We went over 100!
WHAT WILL BECOME OF DESCEND CLUB?
We went over 100.
Subtitle translation by: Kim Yeeun